{
    "id": "603e70623fe5455fb14f3d8152e3bc10",
    "title": "Sentence Linkers Exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "4766879d9fb84d23bbfb04ac003918fa",
            "title": "Sentence Linkers Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "He owns a car ................................ a bike.",
                    "description": "Use either as well as or and here.",
                    "answers": [
                        "as well as",
                        "and",
                        "and as well as"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "It rained ............................... the afternoon.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "during",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "He developed a Canadian accent .............................. his stay in Canada.",
                    "description": "Use during when we are talking about the whole of a period.",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "while",
                        "during"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "His success is largely ............................... his hard work.",
                    "description": "We do not normally use owing to after a form of be.",
                    "answers": [
                        "due to",
                        "because of",
                        "owing to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The night was ................................ dark that I could not see anything.",
                    "description": "The conjunction so..that... expresses cause and effect.",
                    "answers": [
                        "so",
                        "too",
                        "very"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Someone broke into their home .................................. they were holidaying in Venice.",
                    "description": "While can show time.",
                    "answers": [
                        "while",
                        "during",
                        "as"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He opened the garage .............................. took his things out.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "and",
                        "or",
                        "to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": ".................................. his illness he could not attend the party.",
                    "description": "All of these expressions mean the same.",
                    "answers": [
                        "Due to",
                        "Owing to",
                        "Because of",
                        "All of these"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                },
                {
                    "question": "I was working on a new project ............................... last summer.",
                    "description": "We use during when we are talking about the whole of a period. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "during",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She was ............................... upset that she started crying.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "so",
                        "very",
                        "too"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I befriended a lot of Americans ................................. I was holidaying in Chicago.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "during",
                        "while",
                        "then"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I befriended a lot of Americans ………………………… my holiday in Chicago.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "while",
                        "during",
                        "in"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}